# MAC GOUTELL

303 912 0551 • GOUTELLMAC@GMAIL.COM • GITHUB.COM/GOUTELLMAC

#### **SUMMARY**

My interest in software development can be traced back to when I was 12 years old. It was then that I learned about game modification through add-ons. That discovery opened my eyes to the immense potential for creativity and self-education in software development. Ultimately this interest led me to the SeedPaths software development boot camp. The program tested my tenacity and intellectual capabilities while honing my professionalism and software development skills. As a graduate of the SeedPaths program I am eager to prove my worth to your company as an entry-level software developer.

#### **SKILLS**

- \* C#
- Java
- JavaScript
- jQuery

- \* SQL
- Microsoft OS
- GitHub
- HTML & CSS

- AngularJS
- Visual Studio
- · .NET
- C+

### **EDUCATION**

SeedPaths – Denver, CO

2015

 Intensive professional and software development boot camp focused on the fundamentals of object-oriented programming and full stack .NET technologies

## Arapahoe Community College - Centennial, CO

2012-2014

- Completed 25 credits in Game Design and Development
- \* Classes included: Java, Java II, Game Design, and Intro To Programming

## Colorado State University - Fort Collins, CO

2010-2012

Completed two years of coursework in Business Studies

## Arapahoe High School - Centennial, CO

2006-2010

- ❖ Maintained 3.5 GPA for 4 years
- ❖ Co-captained varsity soccer team that made it to State Semi-Finals in 2010

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Perfect Pools – Centennial, CO

2013-2015

Property Manager

- Maintained working order of three private pools to ensure quality experience for neighborhood guests
- \* Used predetermined formulas to measure and properly adjust chemicals to meet cleanliness requirements

Green Touch - Centennial, CO

2013-2015

Manual Laborer / Driver

\* Removed snow from dozens of large commercial and personal residences each night according to a strict schedule and at times worked up to 24 hour shifts in the event of severe weather

References available upon request